module.exports = [
  {
    id: "01c565a7-c600-46f5-9041-3c64915d933e",
    question: "What's the Lords name from Shrek?",
    answers: ["Ralf", "Frederick", "Farquaad", "Fransquad"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    id: "f363c671-e1fc-4f70-875d-c07fa4bb5784",
    question: "What kind of food does Shrek compare himself to?",
    answers: ["apple", "onion", "orange", "pencil"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    id: "634d51b8-5f27-4ce0-944a-dd6216065231",
    question: "what Animal is donkeys wife?",
    answers: ["donkey", "cat", "dragon", "lizard"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    id: "10fcfa92-798a-48da-b686-92083f1279c0",
    question: "what was wrong with Lord Farquaad?",
    answers: ["too short", "too fat", "too tall", "too thin"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    id: "2b436dd4-1a68-4182-b49e-738c283ff36c",
    question: "what is the Kingdom of Shrek called?",
    answers: ["nearby place", "corner land", "greenverse", "far far away"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    id: "d11cdeac-b650-4a67-8144-19363e7cbd42",
    question:
      "what is the very first thing that Shrek says in the second Movie?",
    answers: [
      "I missed the smell",
      "It's good to be home",
      "I need to eat",
      "Get out of my swamp!",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    id: "aee06bb1-912f-495c-971a-adf9269fa417",
    question: "What's the name of Shreks wife?",
    answers: ["Rapunzel", "Puss", "Fiona", "Florida"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    id: "4990ae41-b99d-40ff-9adf-42eb40d4bc1b",
    question: "in the beginning of Shrek 1 what does Shrek put in his drink?",
    answers: ["eyeball", "ear", "hair", "water"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    id: "f68f2394-dd52-46a6-a410-a4b28bd4621f",
    question:
      "what does the Gingerbread man say when Farquaad asks him where the others are?",
    answers: ["fuck you", "shut up shorty", "eat me!", "no"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    id: "3689401b-87f1-4cee-b921-d597a8aca2fe",
    question: "where does Shrek live?",
    answers: ["2 room apartment", "swamp", "castle", "in his car"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
];
